{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946853703374","data":{"timestamp":" 946853703373"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946853703475","data":{"timestamp":" 946853703475"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" bde3dd70-b5f0-4541-896b-7cb379ea7242"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZETU"," userResponse":" ZETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946853782935","data":{"timestamp":" 946853782935"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 9395eba0-7c5d-4692-8bca-e448f075274a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946853805885","data":{"timestamp":" 946853805885"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 9395eba0-7c5d-4692-8bca-e448f075274a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946853829628","data":{"timestamp":" 946853829627"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 9395eba0-7c5d-4692-8bca-e448f075274a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946853832206","data":{"timestamp":" 946853832205"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 9395eba0-7c5d-4692-8bca-e448f075274a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946853863173","data":{"timestamp":" 946853863172"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 9395eba0-7c5d-4692-8bca-e448f075274a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946853865700","data":{"timestamp":" 946853865699"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 9395eba0-7c5d-4692-8bca-e448f075274a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946853868763","data":{"timestamp":" 946853868762"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 9395eba0-7c5d-4692-8bca-e448f075274a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946853897204","data":{"timestamp":" 946853897204"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 9395eba0-7c5d-4692-8bca-e448f075274a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946853899782","data":{"timestamp":" 946853899782"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 9395eba0-7c5d-4692-8bca-e448f075274a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946853920021","data":{"timestamp":" 946853920019"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 9395eba0-7c5d-4692-8bca-e448f075274a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946853920132","data":{"timestamp":" 946853920132"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 9395eba0-7c5d-4692-8bca-e448f075274a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946853932300","data":{"timestamp":" 946853932299"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" ad4129f3-1281-4616-9f50-3c4f3b4d4fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946853933375","data":{"timestamp":" 946853933374"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" ad4129f3-1281-4616-9f50-3c4f3b4d4fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946853933677","data":{"timestamp":" 946853933677"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" ad4129f3-1281-4616-9f50-3c4f3b4d4fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946853933750","data":{"timestamp":" 946853933750"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" ad4129f3-1281-4616-9f50-3c4f3b4d4fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946853951555","data":{"timestamp":" 946853951555"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 81dec2bd-9c99-4d0f-a02c-85d407c963b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946853952422","data":{"timestamp":" 946853952421"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 81dec2bd-9c99-4d0f-a02c-85d407c963b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946853953970","data":{"timestamp":" 946853953970"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 81dec2bd-9c99-4d0f-a02c-85d407c963b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946853984507","data":{"timestamp":" 946853984506"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 81dec2bd-9c99-4d0f-a02c-85d407c963b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946853996290","data":{"timestamp":" 946853996290"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 81dec2bd-9c99-4d0f-a02c-85d407c963b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854013411","data":{"timestamp":" 946854013411"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 81dec2bd-9c99-4d0f-a02c-85d407c963b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854023167","data":{"timestamp":" 946854023167"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 81dec2bd-9c99-4d0f-a02c-85d407c963b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854041737","data":{"timestamp":" 946854041737"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 4392f933-f35c-4a61-acf8-9b6a06c5851d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854045693","data":{"timestamp":" 946854045692"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 4392f933-f35c-4a61-acf8-9b6a06c5851d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854049631","data":{"timestamp":" 946854049631"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 4392f933-f35c-4a61-acf8-9b6a06c5851d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_f-v-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854053502","data":{"timestamp":" 946854053502"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 4392f933-f35c-4a61-acf8-9b6a06c5851d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-B-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854057807","data":{"timestamp":" 946854057807"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 4392f933-f35c-4a61-acf8-9b6a06c5851d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854065105","data":{"timestamp":" 946854065105"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 4392f933-f35c-4a61-acf8-9b6a06c5851d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854070698","data":{"timestamp":" 946854070698"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 4392f933-f35c-4a61-acf8-9b6a06c5851d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" C"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854074815","data":{"timestamp":" 946854074815"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 4392f933-f35c-4a61-acf8-9b6a06c5851d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854078591","data":{"timestamp":" 946854078591"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 4392f933-f35c-4a61-acf8-9b6a06c5851d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854082437","data":{"timestamp":" 946854082437"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 4392f933-f35c-4a61-acf8-9b6a06c5851d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-I-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854087816","data":{"timestamp":" 946854087816"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 4392f933-f35c-4a61-acf8-9b6a06c5851d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_T-I-J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854091926","data":{"timestamp":" 946854091926"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 4392f933-f35c-4a61-acf8-9b6a06c5851d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_B-R-K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854096086","data":{"timestamp":" 946854096086"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 4392f933-f35c-4a61-acf8-9b6a06c5851d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-I-J"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854103393","data":{"timestamp":" 946854103393"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 4392f933-f35c-4a61-acf8-9b6a06c5851d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-W-N"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854108884","data":{"timestamp":" 946854108884"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 4392f933-f35c-4a61-acf8-9b6a06c5851d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854114495","data":{"timestamp":" 946854114494"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 4392f933-f35c-4a61-acf8-9b6a06c5851d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854119756","data":{"timestamp":" 946854119756"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 4392f933-f35c-4a61-acf8-9b6a06c5851d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-D-R"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854127293","data":{"timestamp":" 946854127292"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 4392f933-f35c-4a61-acf8-9b6a06c5851d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-P-B"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854132784","data":{"timestamp":" 946854132784"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 4392f933-f35c-4a61-acf8-9b6a06c5851d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_e-S-n"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854138138","data":{"timestamp":" 946854138138"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 4392f933-f35c-4a61-acf8-9b6a06c5851d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-J-F"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854147201","data":{"timestamp":" 946854147201"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 4392f933-f35c-4a61-acf8-9b6a06c5851d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854154774","data":{"timestamp":" 946854154774"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 4392f933-f35c-4a61-acf8-9b6a06c5851d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-U-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854161288","data":{"timestamp":" 946854161288"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 4392f933-f35c-4a61-acf8-9b6a06c5851d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854168722","data":{"timestamp":" 946854168722"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 4392f933-f35c-4a61-acf8-9b6a06c5851d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854173634","data":{"timestamp":" 946854173634"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 4392f933-f35c-4a61-acf8-9b6a06c5851d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854179403","data":{"timestamp":" 946854179402"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 4392f933-f35c-4a61-acf8-9b6a06c5851d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854212084","data":{"timestamp":" 946854212084"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 2af02f21-8a6f-4e58-b176-35a497e83a7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854214254","data":{"timestamp":" 946854214254"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 2af02f21-8a6f-4e58-b176-35a497e83a7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854216476","data":{"timestamp":" 946854216476"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 2af02f21-8a6f-4e58-b176-35a497e83a7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854229376","data":{"timestamp":" 946854229375"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 2af02f21-8a6f-4e58-b176-35a497e83a7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854229432","data":{"timestamp":" 946854229431"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 2af02f21-8a6f-4e58-b176-35a497e83a7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALE"," userResponse":" YALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854239907","data":{"timestamp":" 946854239907"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 0b96785f-07b3-4392-a3d2-1a61149007a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RUKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUKA"," userResponse":" RUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854242611","data":{"timestamp":" 946854242610"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 0b96785f-07b3-4392-a3d2-1a61149007a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RUKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUKA"," userResponse":" RUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854244188","data":{"timestamp":" 946854244188"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 0b96785f-07b3-4392-a3d2-1a61149007a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RAMANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAMANI"," userResponse":" RAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854246947","data":{"timestamp":" 946854246947"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 0b96785f-07b3-4392-a3d2-1a61149007a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RAMANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAMANI"," userResponse":" RAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854248536","data":{"timestamp":" 946854248535"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 0b96785f-07b3-4392-a3d2-1a61149007a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" REDIO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" REDIO"," userResponse":" REDIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854251880","data":{"timestamp":" 946854251880"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 0b96785f-07b3-4392-a3d2-1a61149007a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" REDIO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" REDIO"," userResponse":" REDIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854253511","data":{"timestamp":" 946854253510"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 0b96785f-07b3-4392-a3d2-1a61149007a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RANGI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854257522","data":{"timestamp":" 946854257522"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 0b96785f-07b3-4392-a3d2-1a61149007a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RANGI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854259117","data":{"timestamp":" 946854259116"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 0b96785f-07b3-4392-a3d2-1a61149007a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RAFIKI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854261951","data":{"timestamp":" 946854261951"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 0b96785f-07b3-4392-a3d2-1a61149007a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RAFIKI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854263572","data":{"timestamp":" 946854263572"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 0b96785f-07b3-4392-a3d2-1a61149007a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RAHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHA"," userResponse":" RAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854265983","data":{"timestamp":" 946854265983"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 0b96785f-07b3-4392-a3d2-1a61149007a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RAHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHA"," userResponse":" RAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854267603","data":{"timestamp":" 946854267603"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 0b96785f-07b3-4392-a3d2-1a61149007a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RINDA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RINDA"," userResponse":" RINDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854273319","data":{"timestamp":" 946854273318"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 0b96785f-07b3-4392-a3d2-1a61149007a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RINDA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RINDA"," userResponse":" RINDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854274935","data":{"timestamp":" 946854274935"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 0b96785f-07b3-4392-a3d2-1a61149007a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RADHI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RADHI"," userResponse":" RADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854277487","data":{"timestamp":" 946854277487"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 0b96785f-07b3-4392-a3d2-1a61149007a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RADHI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RADHI"," userResponse":" RADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854279088","data":{"timestamp":" 946854279087"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 0b96785f-07b3-4392-a3d2-1a61149007a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RUNINGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUNINGA"," userResponse":" RUNINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854281704","data":{"timestamp":" 946854281704"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 0b96785f-07b3-4392-a3d2-1a61149007a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RUNINGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUNINGA"," userResponse":" RUNINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854283711","data":{"timestamp":" 946854283710"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 0b96785f-07b3-4392-a3d2-1a61149007a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" RUNINGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854283828","data":{"timestamp":" 946854283828"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 0b96785f-07b3-4392-a3d2-1a61149007a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RUNINGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUNINGA"," userResponse":" RUNINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854299548","data":{"timestamp":" 946854299548"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 2da9a084-52c0-4c09-a3ff-6dd71d1814f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_1-0-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854306514","data":{"timestamp":" 946854306514"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 2da9a084-52c0-4c09-a3ff-6dd71d1814f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-6-8"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854313327","data":{"timestamp":" 946854313327"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 2da9a084-52c0-4c09-a3ff-6dd71d1814f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-7-3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854318305","data":{"timestamp":" 946854318305"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 2da9a084-52c0-4c09-a3ff-6dd71d1814f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_2-3-1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854324360","data":{"timestamp":" 946854324360"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 2da9a084-52c0-4c09-a3ff-6dd71d1814f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_9-7-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854329662","data":{"timestamp":" 946854329662"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 2da9a084-52c0-4c09-a3ff-6dd71d1814f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_9-7-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854337907","data":{"timestamp":" 946854337907"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 2da9a084-52c0-4c09-a3ff-6dd71d1814f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-7-2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854344489","data":{"timestamp":" 946854344489"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 2da9a084-52c0-4c09-a3ff-6dd71d1814f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_9-6-4"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854353708","data":{"timestamp":" 946854353708"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 2da9a084-52c0-4c09-a3ff-6dd71d1814f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-3-1"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854363659","data":{"timestamp":" 946854363659"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 2da9a084-52c0-4c09-a3ff-6dd71d1814f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_2-3-8"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854371154","data":{"timestamp":" 946854371154"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 2da9a084-52c0-4c09-a3ff-6dd71d1814f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-6-7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854377719","data":{"timestamp":" 946854377719"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 2da9a084-52c0-4c09-a3ff-6dd71d1814f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-6-7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854387593","data":{"timestamp":" 946854387593"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" ae0cdc9e-be1f-46d0-8f73-24b6d1eaa7f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_Z-H-R"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854391856","data":{"timestamp":" 946854391856"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" ae0cdc9e-be1f-46d0-8f73-24b6d1eaa7f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_M-R-D"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854397211","data":{"timestamp":" 946854397211"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" ae0cdc9e-be1f-46d0-8f73-24b6d1eaa7f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-W-Z"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854402066","data":{"timestamp":" 946854402066"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" ae0cdc9e-be1f-46d0-8f73-24b6d1eaa7f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_G-R-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854411733","data":{"timestamp":" 946854411732"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" ae0cdc9e-be1f-46d0-8f73-24b6d1eaa7f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-Y-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854431644","data":{"timestamp":" 946854431644"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" ae0cdc9e-be1f-46d0-8f73-24b6d1eaa7f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_G-R-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854432289","data":{"timestamp":" 946854432289"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" ae0cdc9e-be1f-46d0-8f73-24b6d1eaa7f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_R_G-R-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854448691","data":{"timestamp":" 946854448690"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" ae0cdc9e-be1f-46d0-8f73-24b6d1eaa7f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_R_G-R-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:R..R.all.10.rand.say.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854470970","data":{"timestamp":" 946854470970"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" c4d4d621-f47b-45c2-9ad5-6e3c3b82d854"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_R..R.all.10.rand.say.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_S_Z_R"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:R..R.all.10.rand.say.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854478418","data":{"timestamp":" 946854478418"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" c4d4d621-f47b-45c2-9ad5-6e3c3b82d854"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_R..R.all.10.rand.say.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_S_Z_R"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:R..R.all.10.rand.say.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854485082","data":{"timestamp":" 946854485082"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" c4d4d621-f47b-45c2-9ad5-6e3c3b82d854"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_R..R.all.10.rand.say.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_N_R_B"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:R..R.all.10.rand.say.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854492681","data":{"timestamp":" 946854492681"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" c4d4d621-f47b-45c2-9ad5-6e3c3b82d854"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_R..R.all.10.rand.say.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_N_R_B"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:R..R.all.10.rand.say.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854499316","data":{"timestamp":" 946854499316"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" c4d4d621-f47b-45c2-9ad5-6e3c3b82d854"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_R..R.all.10.rand.say.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_R_S_U"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:R..R.all.10.rand.say.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854505941","data":{"timestamp":" 946854505941"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" c4d4d621-f47b-45c2-9ad5-6e3c3b82d854"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_R..R.all.10.rand.say.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_V_W_R"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:R..R.all.10.rand.say.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854513467","data":{"timestamp":" 946854513467"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" c4d4d621-f47b-45c2-9ad5-6e3c3b82d854"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_R..R.all.10.rand.say.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_V_W_R"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:R..R.all.10.rand.say.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854520087","data":{"timestamp":" 946854520086"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" c4d4d621-f47b-45c2-9ad5-6e3c3b82d854"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_R..R.all.10.rand.say.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_R_O_H"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:R..R.all.10.rand.say.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854526745","data":{"timestamp":" 946854526745"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" c4d4d621-f47b-45c2-9ad5-6e3c3b82d854"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_R..R.all.10.rand.say.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_V_Y_R"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:R..R.all.10.rand.say.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854533358","data":{"timestamp":" 946854533358"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" c4d4d621-f47b-45c2-9ad5-6e3c3b82d854"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_R..R.all.10.rand.say.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_W_N_R"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:R..R.all.10.rand.say.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854540044","data":{"timestamp":" 946854540044"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" c4d4d621-f47b-45c2-9ad5-6e3c3b82d854"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_R..R.all.10.rand.say.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_R_J_D"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:R..R.all.10.rand.say.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854547499","data":{"timestamp":" 946854547499"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" c4d4d621-f47b-45c2-9ad5-6e3c3b82d854"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_R..R.all.10.rand.say.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_R_J_D"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:R..R.all.10.rand.say.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854554184","data":{"timestamp":" 946854554184"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" c4d4d621-f47b-45c2-9ad5-6e3c3b82d854"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_R..R.all.10.rand.say.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_R_J_W"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:R..R.all.10.rand.say.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854560874","data":{"timestamp":" 946854560874"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" c4d4d621-f47b-45c2-9ad5-6e3c3b82d854"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_R..R.all.10.rand.say.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_R_D_E"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:R..R.all.10.rand.say.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854569931","data":{"timestamp":" 946854569931"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" c4d4d621-f47b-45c2-9ad5-6e3c3b82d854"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_R..R.all.10.rand.say.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_R_D_E"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854590965","data":{"timestamp":" 946854590965"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 0fa8f62d-5e09-41f9-b2e4-b27c00e52d15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_1-5-9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854598358","data":{"timestamp":" 946854598358"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 0fa8f62d-5e09-41f9-b2e4-b27c00e52d15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-7-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854603234","data":{"timestamp":" 946854603234"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 0fa8f62d-5e09-41f9-b2e4-b27c00e52d15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-7-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854606678","data":{"timestamp":" 946854606677"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 0fa8f62d-5e09-41f9-b2e4-b27c00e52d15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-7-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:R..R.all.10.rand.say.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854615628","data":{"timestamp":" 946854615628"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 0fa8f62d-5e09-41f9-b2e4-b27c00e52d15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-7-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854621837","data":{"timestamp":" 946854621836"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" 0fa8f62d-5e09-41f9-b2e4-b27c00e52d15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-7-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854631828","data":{"timestamp":" 946854631827"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" ea6e62e1-dd1d-490e-a95f-365ef3aacbf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_K-W-R"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854639948","data":{"timestamp":" 946854639948"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" ea6e62e1-dd1d-490e-a95f-365ef3aacbf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_E-T-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854644486","data":{"timestamp":" 946854644485"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" ea6e62e1-dd1d-490e-a95f-365ef3aacbf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_V-I-R"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854651295","data":{"timestamp":" 946854651294"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" ea6e62e1-dd1d-490e-a95f-365ef3aacbf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_E-R-M"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854658495","data":{"timestamp":" 946854658495"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" ea6e62e1-dd1d-490e-a95f-365ef3aacbf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_Z-T-R"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854663503","data":{"timestamp":" 946854663503"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" ea6e62e1-dd1d-490e-a95f-365ef3aacbf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-G-M"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854667401","data":{"timestamp":" 946854667401"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" ea6e62e1-dd1d-490e-a95f-365ef3aacbf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_G-Z-R"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854672119","data":{"timestamp":" 946854672119"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" ea6e62e1-dd1d-490e-a95f-365ef3aacbf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-G-W"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854679645","data":{"timestamp":" 946854679645"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" ea6e62e1-dd1d-490e-a95f-365ef3aacbf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_O-H-R"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854685327","data":{"timestamp":" 946854685326"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" ea6e62e1-dd1d-490e-a95f-365ef3aacbf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-K-U"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854690401","data":{"timestamp":" 946854690401"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" ea6e62e1-dd1d-490e-a95f-365ef3aacbf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-K-U"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854694381","data":{"timestamp":" 946854694381"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_015150"," gameId":" ea6e62e1-dd1d-490e-a95f-365ef3aacbf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-K-U"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}